module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Bryant Gumbel is best known for hosting what show?', 
    a: 'Nightline',
    b: 'Let\'s Make A Deal',
    c: 'NBC\'s "Today"',
    d: 'The Weakest Link',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Motown records started in which U.S. city?', 
    a: 'Detroit',
    b: 'Atlanta',
    c: 'New York',
    d: 'Nashville',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What TV shows was a spinoff of Cheers and featured David Hyde Pierce?', 
    a: 'Spin City',
    b: 'Step by Step',
    c: 'Mad About You',
    d: 'Frasier',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What term describes the temperature at which cooled water vapor turns into liquid water?', 
    a: 'Saturation Point',
    b: 'Dew Point',
    c: 'Evaporation',
    d: 'Relative Humidity',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who painted the 1930 painting "American Gothic"?', 
    a: 'Grant Wood',
    b: 'Edvard Munch',
    c: 'Vincent van Gogh',
    d: 'Salvador Dali',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What Nu Metal band formed in 1993 and features Jonathan Davis on vocals?', 
    a: 'Limp Bizkit',
    b: 'Korn',
    c: 'Deftones',
    d: 'Papa Roach',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many calories are in a McDonald\'s Big Mac?', 
    a: '390',
    b: '540',
    c: '780',
    d: '860',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What organization assigns top-level domains like ".com", ".org", and ".net"?', 
    a: 'IANA',
    b: 'IETF',
    c: 'ICANN',
    d: 'IMAP',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The album "40 Oz. To Freedom" was produced in 1992 by which band?', 
    a: 'Sublime',
    b: 'No Doubt',
    c: 'Nirvana',
    d: 'Weezer',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Also known as "Zone Therapy," which alternative medicine involves applying pressure to the hands or feet?', 
    a: 'Homeopathy',
    b: 'Shiatsu',
    c: 'Reiki',
    d: 'Reflexology',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];